(Leonard:)We're trying to get past
a security guard,
(Leonard:)not rescue Zelda.
(Sheldon:)I think what really needs to be
rescued is your sense of whimsy,
(Sheldon:)but one quest at a time.
(Sheldon:)So what's the plan?
(Leonard:)Uh, I'm just gonna be honest
with the guy.
(Sheldon:)Honesty will never
get us in.
(Leonard:)Well, what's
your plan?
(Sheldon:)All right, my plan is
predicated on the assumption
(Sheldon:)that they have
a nurse's office
(Sheldon:)and your willingness
to be lightly stabbed.
(Security Guard:)Who are you here to see?
(Leonard:)Uh, I'm just gonna
tell you the truth.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you are killing me.
(Leonard:)We don't have
an appointment.
We-we're just fans
of Mr. Lucas's work,
(Leonard:)and we thought
we'd take a shot
(Leonard:)and see if we could get in
and look around.
(Security Guard:)Sorry, guys, we get this a lot.
(Security Guard:)Can't let you in.
(Sheldon:)What if I told you
that I was the voice of Yoda?
(imitating Yoda): A recording
session I must attend.